You can't have summer vacation without...
the beach!
Good thing we took a spontaneous trip
to this deserted island!
U-uh, sure.
But the swimsuit that the boss
brought for me is...
I could probaby win a
sexual harassment case with it.
On second thought, I'm going to go change-
Sorry we're late!
Yay, the ocean!
And what lovely weather! How delightful!
Laika can't wait to munch on
the fish she catches.
Miss Boss Lady.
You have my sincerest gratitude for not only
looking after my niece and her friends,
but also selecting swimwear for us.
Don't sweat it! I invited you here, after all.
Alright, everyone!
We have until the boat picks us up,
so let's party!
Yeah!
Plus-Sized Elf
Muffin Top Island
Why did I have to come...?
Are you okay?
Dragging me to a deserted island and
forcing me to wear this obscene outfit...
It's absolutely unaccept-
Wh-what the hell are you wearing?!
You're a creep!
A creep?!
She's always griping about something...
We captured the satyr when she
snuck into the human's place,
but maybe we shouldn't have brought her...
Staaaaare...
...just do it...
What?
If you're going to laugh,
just get it over with!
Hey there, little one.
Wanna build a sandcastle with Mommy?
I'm in hell...
Oh my! Isn't playing in the sand wonderful?
I'm a pro at it, too!
B-back off, you two!
She only needs one mom and it's ME!
I don't know if I'm cut out to be a mother...
I don't really care either way.
Craaab...
Are you sure it's safe to jump...?
Relax, we'll be fine!
It looks like fun!
Check this out! I'll go first!
Oh, but Miss Merrow... I thought
you couldn't swim in human f-
Look out below!
She's in trouble!
I'm coming to save y-
I never learned to swim either...
What?! Then why would you jump?!
Miss Doggie, what should we-
Floaty...
Ah, that feels fantastic...
Naoe, you're so skilled with your hands...
A creep...
There's a creep among us...
Noisy two-legged miscreants...
I will purge them from my ocean!
What is this thing?
A stand up paddle board,
also known as a "SUP."
It's an aquatic sport enjoyed by
adults and children alike!
You have to stand on the board
and maintain your balance,
which means you get a full-body workout.
Since it's a steady surface,
you can even do yoga on top of it.
Seems simple enough.
Must be a nice board if it doesn't sink
under the weight of Elfatty.
Excuse me?!
C-calm down, ladies!
Our feet can touch the bottom here!
Don't drag me down too, humungo-butt!
Oh, shut up! I wasn't anywhere near you!
There must be something wrong with my board!
It just flipped over for no reason!
Hmm, it's actually pretty tough
to fall off like that...
Auntie!
We're busy drownin' while they're
out there havin' a grand old time.
I wouldn't mind giving it a try...
Mobile home crab...
Squid?
Miss Doggie?!
The heck happened?!
Miss Dog?! Are you alright?!
What is this?! A booby trap?!
I get the feeling someone
wants to ruin our day...
Are you okay, Miss Pig?!
That scared me...
She freed herself?!
Wait, where's your swimsuit?!
It slipped off.
Help us, Miss Dog!
Save Miss Pig first!
It's the most effective approach for
disposing of unwanted pests...
Wear them down with small inconveniences!
The slow burn method is insquidious!
For my next victim...
Floaty, floaty...
Come to think of it,
what's a dragon doing here...?
No matter.
Dragon or not, it is I who
reigns supreme in the water!
Moms are strong!
Are we still doing this...?
The last one standing inside this circle
will be crowned the ultimate mom!
A wrestling match between the three of us?
I don't think I can win...
I'm not interested in being a mother...
but it's time we settle this feud
once and for all.
Then here goes nothing.
Good luck!
Aren'tcha gonna fight?
I'd die if I tried to take on
a couple of giants.
So they're giants, not just big-boned...
As forsquidable as I am,
if I got caught up in their duel on land...
Take this!
No... I am an emperor!
Unrelenting! Undaunted! Undefeated!
C'mon, ladies!
Let's get the barbeque started!
Temporary truce.
Agreed.
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
Wow, what a spread!
So many ingredients to choose from.
And they're all fresh.
Looks tasty...
Squid is yet another great option
when you're watching your weight.
But the boss fell asleep,
and she was supposed to slice it up...
Oh jeez... Stop that, Naoe...
Well, she did drink quite a bit...
What do we do now...?
Not to fret, human!
Elfuda-
I made my own French fries just in case
something like this happened!
Seems like it's finally my time to shine!
Preparing squid is a piece of cake.
Let me handle this!
Fine, whatever. But, uh...
Your swimsuit.
Huh?
NOOOOO!
Is that a...?!
I won't abide treating
my brethren like garbage!
An earthquake?!
Enough squidding around!
They'll pay for tresspassing in my ocean!
The hell is that?!
Is that a kraken?!
A kraken...?
A giant squid, and it's extremely territorial.
I'd heard it was ousted as king of the seas,
but I wasn't aware it had migrated
to the human world...
I-I wasn't "ousted"!
I simply had a cold that day!
Otherwise, I would've blown those
squidiots out of the water!
That sounds like a pretty lame excuse...
It's not an excuse, it's the TRUTH!
You dare defy me?!
Quit your yapping!
Potato Strike!
Foolish creature.
You think you can best me?
Tsk, I can't get close enough...
W-we're dead meat!
No need to panic, human.
Witness our combat prowess in action.
Wait a second...!
We need a replacement squid
for the barbeque, don't we?
We'll take care of it.
Whichever of us defeats the kraken
is her REAL mom!
Don't I get a say in this?!
Hoist it onto the beach!
Pull! Pull! Pull! Pull!
Hmph, how pathetic...
Looks yummy...
Don't eat me!
Enchantment!
Let's do this!
Hyaaaaa!
Mommy Power!
It's useless! Futile!
Your attacks are mere child's play
to the Almighty Kraken.
You bottom feeders don't stand a chance
against one such as I.
Eek!
So this was YOUR doing...
You shall rue the day...
you dared lay a tentacle on me!
Oh squid!
Dragon Breath!
Whoa, take it easy!
You'll blast the others too!
IT BURNS!
It's finawwy over...
Thank goodness.
Laika wanted calamari...
Why isn't there anything to eat?
That's your fault!
C'mon, human. Hang in there.
Naoe smells like a seaman...